natural-fertility-info.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy

At Natural Fertility Info.com, your privacy is very important to us. We do not sell or otherwise share customer, or personally identifying information, with other people or companies unless to provide services to you at your request, or as required by law. We understand that the protection of privacy is a major concern to many of our customers.

You can [contact us via e-mail](http://natural-fertility-info.com/contact-us) or you can reach us by telephone at 1-800-851-7957

We may collect information about visitors that is used to improve the content of our Website. Information may include domain names, aggregate (i.e. non-personally identifiable) information on what pages consumers access or visit, user –specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey or contest entry information and/or site registrations. When personal information is volunteered, we may utilize that information internally to better understand our web user’s behavior and patterns to better serve you.

We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. Our Website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such websites. 

Natural Fertility Info.com strives to take all reasonable steps to have physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in place to protect personal information gathered through our Website. This includes compliance with related federal regulations and may include use of industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect certain data we deem sensitive. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your personal information private and will not share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with court order or other legal process; or (b) protect our rights or property. 

Your use of our Website, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Website. BY USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on our Website without any other notice to you. Any such modification shall be effective immediately upon posting on our Website. Please check the effective date below to determine if the policy has been updated or modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of our Website following posting of the updated or modified Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included at the bottom of the email.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an [e-mail](http://natural-fertility-info.com/contact-us) and include REMOVE in the subject line or your e-mail.

**Questions & Comments**  
Natural Fertility Info.com is always interested in what our customers have to say. If you have any questions or concerns, please [contact us here](http://natural-fertility-info.com/contact-us).

Our postal address is:  
The Natural Fertility Company  
313918 E Mississippi Ave #67080  
Aurora, CO 80012

This document was last updated April 1st, 2016.

If you feel this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us via phone, e-mail or mail.

Hethir Rodriguez is the Founder and President of Natural Fertility Info.com. She has been a Certified Herbalist for over 19 years, holds a Bachelors degree (BS) in Nutrition Sciences and is a Certified Birth Doula.  Since founding Natural Fertility Info.com in 2007, Hethir has written and co-authored over 1200+ articles on Fertility; and her research, articles, and guides have been read by over 40,000,000 people.  Hethir has dedicated her life to helping provide a source for high quality, research based information and support for those on their journey to becoming parents.
